<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Leave Management App</title>
    <link>http://onleaveapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Simple Leave Management App</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://onleaveapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms-conditions:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Terms &amp;amp; conditions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: Feb 28, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for choosing Onleave. By accessing or using the Onleave website at www.onleaveapp.com (&amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;) or related services (&amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;), you agree to the following Terms of Service. If you do not agree to the following Terms of Service, do not use the Site or the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnleaveApp (&amp;ldquo;Onleave&amp;rdquo;) reserves the right to modify or replace these Terms of Service at any time and in Onleave&amp;rsquo;s sole discretion. Onleave will indicate at the top of these Terms of Service the date such document was last updated. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting the revised version on the Site (or such later effective date as may be indicated at the top of the revised Terms of Service). Your continued use of the Site or Service following the posting of any changes to these Terms of Service will constitute your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you must stop using the Site and Service. In addition, Onleave may provide other methods by which you may accept these Terms of Service or changes to these Terms of Service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy-policy:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Privacy policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: Feb 28, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy applies to all services provided by OnLeaveApp. (the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;) If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to send us email at rozi [at] onleaveapp [dot] com, with the words &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo; in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnLeave only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to particular purposes described in more detail below, such purposes include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing the Services;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve the Services;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensuring the technical functioning of systems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting the rights or property of OnLeave or its users and customers; and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing new services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 23:53:53 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>