<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Simple Leave Management App</title>
    <link>http://onleaveapp.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Simple Leave Management App</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://onleaveapp.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms-conditions:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Terms &amp;amp; conditions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: Feb 29, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for choosing Onleave. By accessing or using the Onleave website at onleaveapp.com (&amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;) or related services (&amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;), you agree to the following Terms of Service. If you do not agree to the following Terms of Service, do not use the Site or the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnleaveApp (&amp;ldquo;Onleave&amp;rdquo;) reserves the right to modify or replace these Terms of Service at any time and in Onleave&amp;rsquo;s sole discretion. Onleave will indicate at the top of these Terms of Service the date such document was last updated. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting the revised version on the Site (or such later effective date as may be indicated at the top of the revised Terms of Service). Your continued use of the Site or Service following the posting of any changes to these Terms of Service will constitute your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you must stop using the Site and Service. In addition, Onleave may provide other methods by which you may accept these Terms of Service or changes to these Terms of Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-use-of-site-and-site-materials:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;1. Use of Site and Site Materials&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Site and all the materials on the Site, including without limitation the Onleave logo and all designs, text, graphics, pictures, information and other content (collectively, &amp;ldquo;Site Materials&amp;rdquo;), are the proprietary property of Onleave or its licensors. You are granted a limited, nonexclusive license (without the right to sublicense) to access and use the Site and Site Materials for your personal or internal business use only. Such license is subject to these Terms of Service and excludes: (a) any resale of the Site or any Site Materials; (b) the distribution, public performance or public display of any Site Materials; &amp;copy; modifying or otherwise making any derivative uses of the Site or any Site Materials; (d) use of any data mining, robots or similar data gathering or extraction, automated account registration, or account utilization methods; (e) downloading (other than the page caching) of any portion of the Site, the Site Materials or any information contained therein; or (f) any use of the Site or any Site Materials other than for its intended purpose. Any use of the Site or Site Materials other than as specifically authorized herein is strictly prohibited and will terminate the foregoing license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;2-account-registration-and-security-use-of-the-service:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;2. Account Registration and Security; Use of the Service&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onleave reserves the right to refuse registration, or to refuse or limit access to the Site and the Service, to anyone in its sole discretion for any reason or no reason. You will provide current, complete and accurate identification, contact, and other information about you as may be prompted by the registration process on the Site (&amp;ldquo;Registration Data&amp;rdquo;). You will maintain and promptly update the Registration Data, and any other information you provide to Onleave, to keep it current, complete and accurate. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information, and are responsible for all activities that occur under your account. You agree to immediately notify Onleave of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security relating to the Service. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT ANY PERSON WITH YOUR COMPANY NAME, USERNAME AND PASSWORD WILL BE ABLE TO ACCESS YOUR ACCOUNT, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, REGISTRATION DATA YOU PROVIDE TO ONLEAVE. YOU ACCEPT ALL RISKS OF UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO YOUR ACCOUNT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;3-disclosure-and-use-of-data-and-related-information:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;3. Disclosure and Use of Data and Related Information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onleave uses email addresses, account passwords, and server content, and other information or data you provide to Onleave solely to provide the Service and improve the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;4-acceptable-conduct:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;4. Acceptable Conduct&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree that you are responsible for all information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video, messages, files, attachments or other materials (‘Content’) that is created, transmitted, stored, or displayed by, from, or within the Service using your account. You agree to use the Service only for purposes that are legal, proper and in accordance with these Terms of Service and any applicable policies or guidelines on the Site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;5-prohibited-usage:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;5. Prohibited Usage&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree that any of the below activities are considered prohibited usage, and agree not to engage in the same. You acknowledge that such prohibited usage may result in immediate account suspension or cancellation, in addition to any other remedies Onleave may pursue at law:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disruption of the Service: Engaging in any activity that interferes with or disrupts the Service or Site (including servers or networks connected the Service or Site).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to Other Computers or Networks without Authorization: Attempting unauthorized and/or illegal access of computers, networks and/or accounts not belonging to you seeking access. Any act which interferes with the services of another user or network. Any act relating to the circumvention of security measures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other Activities viewed as Illegal or Harmful: Engaging in illegal activities or engaging in activities harmful to the operations of Onleave or other customers of Onleave.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing False Data on any Contract or Application: including fraudulent use of credit card numbers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resale: Reselling, redistributing or rerouting the Service, or any part of the service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Breach of Third Party Service Agreements: Using the Service in a manner that violates the terms and conditions of a third party cloud service or other service.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;6-account-cancellation-or-suspension-termination:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;6. Account Cancellation or Suspension; Termination&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Onleave may cancel or suspend your access to the Service at any time and for any reason without notice. Upon cancellation or suspension, your right to use the Service will stop immediately. You may terminate the Service at any time by contacting Onleave via the contact page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, Onleave may terminate these Terms of Service at any time, with or without cause, immediately upon notice to you. You may terminate these Terms of Service by cancelling your Onleave account. In the event of the termination of these Terms of Service for any reason: (a) the licenses granted to you in these Terms of Service will terminate; (b) you must immediately cease all use of the Site and Service; and &amp;copy; Section 3 and Sections 6 through 12 will survive any such termination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;7-limitation-of-liability:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;7. Limitation of Liability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ONLEAVE AND ITS AFFILIATES, AND EACH OF THEIR RESPECTIVE MEMBERS, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS (&amp;ldquo;ONLEAVE PARTIES&amp;rdquo;) SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES RESULTING FROM: (I) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR THE SERVICE; (II) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; OR (III) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SITE OR THE SERVICE. YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING IN THE AGREEMENT TO THE CONTRARY, THE MAXIMUM AGGREGATE MONETARY LIABILITY OF THE ONLEAVE PARTIES IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE OR SERVICE, UNDER ANY THEORY OF LAW (INCLUDING BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY, AND INFRINGEMENT), SHALL NOT EXCEED FIFTY MALAYSIAN RINGGIT (RM50.00).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;8-exclusions-and-limitations:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;8. Exclusions and Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing in this agreement is intended to exclude or limit any condition, warranty, right or liability which may not be lawfully excluded or limited.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;9-no-third-party-beneficiaries:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;9. No Third Party Beneficiaries&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree that there shall be no third party beneficiaries to these Terms of Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;10-disclaimers:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;10. Disclaimers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND SERVICE SHALL BE AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITE AND SERVICE ARE PROVIDED AS IS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. ONLEAVE DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT, AS TO THE SITE AND THE SERVICE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-indemnity:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;11. Indemnity&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You agree to indemnify and hold harmless (and at Onleave’s option, defend) the Onleave Parties from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, and expenses (including but not limited to attorney’s fees) arising from or relating to: (i) your use of and access to the Site or Service; (ii) your violation of these Terms of Service; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right, in connection with your use of the Site or Service. This indemnification obligation will survive the termination of your Onleave account or these Terms of Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;12-general:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;12. General&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Entire Agreement. These Terms of Service (together with any other agreement you may enter with Onleave) constitute the entire agreement between you and Onleave regarding your use of the Site and Service, and supersede any prior agreements between you and Onleave for the use of the Onleave Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These terms and conditions are subject to Malaysian law. If any part of them are deemed illegal, for instance as a result of changes in the law, then only that part (and any related part) will no longer be valid. The rest of terms and conditions will still be valid.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Waiver and Severability of Terms. The failure of Onleave to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Service shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms of Service is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, then that provision shall be deemed severed from these Terms of Service and the other provisions of these Terms of Service shall remain in full force and effect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Statute of Limitations. You agree that to the extent permitted by law, any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Site or Service or these Terms of Service must be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;privacy-policy:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Privacy policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: Feb 29, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy applies to all services provided by OnLeave (the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;). If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to send us email at rozi [at] onleaveapp [dot] com, with the words &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo; in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnLeave only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to particular purposes described in more detail below, such purposes include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing the Services;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve the Services;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensuring the technical functioning of systems;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protecting the rights or property of OnLeave or its users and customers; and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing new services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-we-collect:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Information we collect&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We intentionally and explicitly collect certain information about you and your use of the Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personal Information: When you register for a OnLeave account, we ask you for personal information, such as a fullname, email address and an account password. We use this information only to enable the operation of your account, or to send you email related to operation of your account. If you opt-in to receive information about new features and Services, we may send you email for these purposes also.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Payment Information: For some of the Services, we also request credit card or other payment account information, which we neither process nor store, but instead transmit directly and in encrypted form to our third-party credit card processing provider. The third-party provider may store this information, and we may use it indirectly through them to charge your account for Services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cookies: When you use the Services, we send one or more cookies – small files containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to maintain information about your active OnLeave session, but these cookies do not persist beyond the session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Log and Usage History: When you use the Services, we track operational behavior of your usage (including, without limitation, starting servers, installing applications, and other commands available from our console), as well as the general behavior of any cloud servers that you engage (including, without limitation, startup times, system performance and uptime). We also maintain server logs for our company website and for the software that operates the Services, and these server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We may use this information to diagnose problems, operate our system more efficiently, or to produce and publish aggregate statistics across customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support and other Communications: When you send email or other communications to OnLeave, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We may also adapt your inquiries to provide general questions and answers in the form of FAQs, discussion forum questions, or other formats, and we will remove all identifying and unique information prior to such publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statistical Analytics Tool: This website uses Google Analytics to help analyse how users use the site. The tool uses &amp;ldquo;cookies,&amp;rdquo; which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors&amp;rsquo; us of the webiste and to compile statistical reports on website activity for OnLeave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-to-which-we-have-access:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Information to which we have access&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have access to certain information about you and your use of the Services as a by-product of operating the Services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cloud Server Information: When you use the Services to operate application software on cloud servers, the servers maintain information that you enter and/or that is applicable to your operation of the application, including without limitation data stored in a database, browser cookies, server logs, command line history, and the like. Because we control and operate servers for various purposes on your behalf, we have access to this information. Under normal operation, only our automated systems have access to this information; however, we may access the information manually if we determine it is necessary to keep the Services operating properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data Backups: In some cases, the Services provide for data backups. These data backups are encrypted prior to transmission and storage, and we retain the access keys. We will never access or use data backups for any purpose other than to operate the Services, except as provided under Information Sharing below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limited Credit Card Information: After you register your credit card through our credit card processing provider, we may subsequently have access to basic account information such as your name and expiration date, but never the credit card number nor the CVV or similar code. We use this information only to re-populate the credit card page to make changing your credit card information easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-security:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Information security&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. We restrict access to personal information to OnLeave employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applications, including open source applications, that you operate through the Services will run on cloud servers and may be subject to typical security risks of such applications and servers. We take reasonable precautions so as not to increase the inherent security risks of such applications and servers; however, assessment of the security risks of the application and the cloud service are your responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnLeave processes personal information on cloud servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-sharing:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Information sharing&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnLeave only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of the company in the following limited circumstances:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We obtain your consent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You log in or register for our service via a co-branded page, on which notice is provided that your contact information will be shared with a particular third party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have contracted with a third party to process information on our behalf as a component of providing the Services. We require that these parties process such information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, &amp;copy; detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of OnLeave, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If OnLeave becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who installed a particular application, or the average duration of a particular process using OnLeave. Such information does not identify you individually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;modification-and-deletion-of-personal-information:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Modification and deletion of personal information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information so that you can correct this data if it is inaccurate. If you close your account, we may retain your personal information for a reasonable amount of time to ensure an orderly shutdown of both the applicable Services and our business relationship with you, and may use this information to contact you if it is necessary for those purposes. We may subsequently delete your personally identifying information from our systems, but we may retain your usage information indefinitely (but without personally identifying information).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;choices-for-personal-information:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Choices for personal information&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we intend to use your personal information in any manner or for any purpose other than those described in this Privacy Policy, we will ask for your consent prior to such use and will offer you an effective way to opt out of such use; provided, however, that this limitation will not apply to our inclusion or use of such information in aggregate form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, the Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can decline to submit personal information to the Services, in which case OnLeave may not be able to provide those Services to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other-sites:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Other sites&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy applies to OnLeave services only. We do not exercise control over sites to which we link, including without limitation open source software project sites, software license sites, or cloud service provider sites. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;changes-to-the-privacy-policy:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Changes to the privacy policy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without advance notice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to send us email at rozi [at] onleaveapp [dot] com, with the words &amp;ldquo;Privacy Policy&amp;rdquo; in the subject line.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 23:53:53 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>