<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terms on Simple Leave Management App</title>
    <link>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Terms on Simple Leave Management App</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://onleaveapp.com/terms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 01:24:50 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://onleaveapp.com/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;terms-conditions:d680e8a854a7cbad6d490c445cba2eba&#34;&gt;Terms &amp;amp; conditions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last updated: Feb 28, 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for choosing Onleave. By accessing or using the Onleave website at www.onleaveapp.com (&amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;) or related services (&amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;), you agree to the following Terms of Service. If you do not agree to the following Terms of Service, do not use the Site or the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;OnleaveApp (&amp;ldquo;Onleave&amp;rdquo;) reserves the right to modify or replace these Terms of Service at any time and in Onleave&amp;rsquo;s sole discretion. Onleave will indicate at the top of these Terms of Service the date such document was last updated. Any changes will be effective immediately upon posting the revised version on the Site (or such later effective date as may be indicated at the top of the revised Terms of Service). Your continued use of the Site or Service following the posting of any changes to these Terms of Service will constitute your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree to the changes, you must stop using the Site and Service. In addition, Onleave may provide other methods by which you may accept these Terms of Service or changes to these Terms of Service.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>